Gross, James A., Collection of NLRB 60th Annual Conference Files /4232
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
James A. Gross Collection of NLRB 60th Annual Conference Files
1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Labor Relations Board (NLRB)
Gross, James A.
/4232
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8056651
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 29, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Professor Gross teaches Labor Law, Labor Arbitration, and a course entitled Values, Rights and Justice in Economics, Law, and Industrial Relations. He received his B.S. from LaSalle College, M.A. from Temple University, and Ph.D. from University of Wisconsin.
Professor Gross is a member of National Academy of Arbitrators and on the labor arbitration panels of the American Arbitration Association, Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service and New York State Public Employment Relations Board, as well as being a panelist named in several contracts.[www.ilr.cornell.edu/directory/jag28/biography.htm]
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files /4057 P: James A. Gross NLRB Photographs /4124: James A. Gross Papers, Additional NLRB Research Files /4166: James A. Gross Additional NLRB Research Files /4186: James A. Gross Additional Research Files /4190: James A. Gross Additional Research Files 5697: James A. Gross Arbitration Files 5959: James A. Gross Additional Arbitration Files /4079: James A. Gross Additional Files
Gross, James A., 1933-; National Labor Relations Bureau (U.S.); New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8056651
- James Gross Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- NLRB Conference, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- The Jack Sheinkman Endowment Fund Dinner, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Panel Ideas - NLRB, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Memorandum, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Invitation Lists, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bios, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- NLRB and the Wagner Act, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- ILR Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Anniversary Conference - NLRB Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Invitations, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ILR Press, 1984-1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Conference Participants, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Conference Outlines, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 50th Anniversary Conference, 1984-1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Anniversary Conference - Participants, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Contributions, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- J. Gross (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Scope and Contents
  Box